officearrow.com 2013-04-16

# Privacy Policy - OfficeArrow Marketplace

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the use of www.OfficeArrow.com and any other OfficeArrow-branded URL (collectively, the "OfficeArrow Website") and to the features, content, products, applications, newsletters, other communications, advertising, and services offered from time to time by OfficeArrow in connection with the OfficeArrow Website (the "OfficeArrow Services"). The OfficeArrow Website is hosted in the United States.

This Privacy Policy covers how OfficeArrow collects, uses, and shares information, including personally identifiable information that you provide to us and information we collect automatically when you access and use the OfficeArrow Website and OfficeArrow Services. This Privacy Policy also describes what information of yours is provided to third parties that (i) assist OfficeArrow in providing services to you, (ii) provide services to you directly or via a link from the OfficeArrow Website, (iii) provide services to OfficeArrow, and (iv) advertise on the OfficeArrow Website ("Service Providers"). Service Providers may provide you with certain content, products, applications, or services ("Service Provider Services").

Except as expressly described in this Privacy Policy, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of Service Providers that OfficeArrow does not own or control, or to acts of people that OfficeArrow does not employ or manage.

### 1.0 Information Collection

We collect two types of information: information you voluntarily disclose to us; and information we collect automatically as you interact with the OfficeArrow Website.

Generally, the information you provide to us and that we automatically collect will be used to allow us to respond to your requests and questions, customize your interactions with the OfficeArrow Website, facilitate your interactions with Service Providers, communicate with you about the OfficeArrow Website, allow members of the OfficeArrow Community and visitors to the OfficeArrow Website (collectively, "Participants") to communicate with you, and allow us to compile user data to be used in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

### 1.1 Information You Provide to OfficeArrow

(a) Registration

Anyone is able to view the OfficeArrow Website and navigate through certain Web pages without submitting any information other than the information we automatically collect from all users of the OfficeArrow Website. However, in order to more fully utilize the OfficeArrow Website, we require users to complete an online registration form. Registration with the OfficeArrow Website allows users to become "members" of the "OfficeArrow Community," form relationships with other members, send messages, perform searches and queries, form or join groups, submit content, participate in discussions and forums, participate in contests or surveys, and send and receive information through various channels. Certain other services and functionality may also be available to registered users or "premium members" who pay a subscription fee or purchase a service on an a la carte basis.

When you register with OfficeArrow, you create an account with us by providing a user name and password. During the registration process, you are required to provide us with certain limited personal information, such as your name, email address, and zip code. You may also create an account by means of third party applications such as FacebookTM Connect.

(b) Profiles

Once you have registered with the OfficeArrow Website, you may provide additional information to us by completing your "Profile", a section of your account that holds your personal information.

Portions of your Profile can be made accessible to Participants by making them part of your "Public Profile." The information in your Public Profile may include the city and state where you live, your job title, professional experiences, professional skills, and educational background, among other things. Information in your Public Profile will be made available to Participants in certain situations. In addition, as noted below, personally identifiable information that you submit to the forums and discussions on the OfficeArrow Website or directly to other Participants may remain online for an extended period of time, and we are not responsible for such disclosures.

Information that you place in your Profile but do not make part of your Public Profile will be a part of your "Private Profile." In your Private Profile, you may choose to enter certain information about you, your preferences, your membership in other affinity programs, and other information. Providing this additional information is optional, but providing it may enable you to better utilize and enjoy the OfficeArrow Services and Service Provider Services. The OfficeArrow Site is set up not to provide information in your Private Profile to other Participants. If you subscribe to the OfficeArrow Site for a subscription fee or purchase a product or services from us or one of our Service Providers, you may store Financial Information (described below) as a part of your Private Profile. Certain information in your Private Profile will be made available to Service Providers to assist with the provision of Service Provider Services to you. OfficeArrow will also use information in your Private Profile to provide OfficeArrow Services to you and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

(c) Purchases

If you purchase a product or service from us or from one or our Service Providers, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you in order to process your order and, if necessary, ship your products. If required, you must provide this additional information in order to finalize a purchase. This information will generally be your contact information (such as your mailing address and phone number) (the "Additional Order Information") and your financial information (such as your credit card number, expiration date, and billing address) (the "Financial Information"). Unless you are a subscriber to the OfficeArrow Site and pay a subscription fee or purchase products from a Service Provider that is processed through the OfficeArrow shopping cart, OfficeArrow will not store your Financial Information.

We and our Service Providers use Additional Order Information and Financial Information for billing purposes and to process and ship your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we or our Service Providers will use the Additional Order Information to contact you. If your Additional Order Information is not part of your Profile, we may add it to your Private Profile. We will not store your Financial Information without your permission.

If you purchase a product or service from a Service Provider via a link from the OfficeArrow Website, you are dealing with that Service Provider and OfficeArrow has no responsibility for the transaction or the use of information provided by you or us to the Service Provider. The Service Provider’s privacy policy will apply to the Service Provider’s use of your information. In order to make the transaction process easier for you, we will make the information from your Profile available to the applicable Service Provider necessary or appropriate for the transaction and processing the transaction.

(d) When OfficeArrow’s Privacy Policy or a Service Provider’s Privacy Policy Conflict

Normally, when a Service Provider is providing Service Provider Services to you, the Service Provider’s privacy policy will apply to the gathering and use of information that you and OfficeArrow provide to the Service Provider, and OfficeArrow’s Privacy Policy will not apply. OfficeArrow is not responsible for the use of any of your information provided to a Service Provider in accordance with this Privacy Policy, nor is OfficeArrow responsible for information provided by you to the Service Provider. When receiving Service Provider Services, you will normally see a different look and feel of the Service Provider’s Website and a URL that is different from those of OfficeArrow.

In some situations, the Web pages on which services are provided by a Service Provider will have the same look and feel as the OfficeArrow Website. OfficeArrow does this to provide a consistent experience to you. When Service Provider Services are provided to you on a Web page that has OfficeArrow’s look and feel, then this Privacy Policy will apply, except as follows:

If OfficeArrow places a button or link to a URL for a privacy policy and terms of use prominently on the applicable Web page, then the privacy policy and terms of use identified by that button or link will apply.

(e) Invite a Friend

If you wish to invite a friend to connect with you through the OfficeArrow Website, we will ask you to enter his or her email address into our "Invite a Friend" online form.

This information will be used by OfficeArrow to send your friend a one time, automatically generated email invitation to view the OfficeArrow Website and join the OfficeArrow community. OfficeArrow stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our "Invite a Friend" program. The email will contain information that your friend can use to remove this information from our database.

(f) Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on the OfficeArrow Website. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary; however, if you choose to participate in the contest or survey, you must submit the requested information. If you do not want to submit the requested information, do not participate in the contest or survey. The requested information will typically include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code), but may include other information depending on the nature of the contest or survey.

We use the information submitted in these contests and surveys to determine the winners of the contests, to notify the contest winners and award prizes, to monitor the OfficeArrow Website traffic, and to personalize and improve the OfficeArrow Website. We may use Service Providers to conduct these surveys or contests.

### 1.2 Information OfficeArrow Automatically Collects

This Privacy Policy also covers the use of technology used by OfficeArrow to automatically collect information.

(a) Log Files

Each time you visit the OfficeArrow Website, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes, for example, the domain and host from which you access the Internet, your domain name, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the name of the page that referred you to us, the date and time you access the OfficeArrow Website, the pages you visited, the OfficeArrow partners and advertisers that are accessed from the OfficeArrow Website, and the entry and exit times from the OfficeArrow Website. This information is automatically gathered for all the OfficeArrow Website visitors and Participants.

We use this information, which does not identify you individually, to analyze trends, to administer the OfficeArrow Website, to track users' movements around the OfficeArrow Website, and to gather demographic information about our user base.

(b) Cookies

In addition to log files, we store certain information from your browser using cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer for record keeping purposes. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on the OfficeArrow Website.

We use cookies to make it easier to navigate through the OfficeArrow Website, track and target your interests in order to customize your experience, maintain items in your shopping cart, and otherwise enhance your visits to the OfficeArrow Website. We also use our own cookies to access your information when you sign in and to support security measures such as requiring you to re-log into an OfficeArrow product or service after a certain amount of time has elapsed.

You can remove persistent cookies or prevent your computer from accepting cookies by following the directions provided with your web browser. However, if you disable this feature and do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features of the OfficeArrow Website, including the shopping cart feature.

(c) Web Beacons

We sometimes allow certain Service Providers, called "ad networks," to direct or send advertisements to OfficeArrow users, a process known as "serving advertisements." Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. As noted above, we may "target" some ads to you, meaning that we or our Service Providers may select ads with certain characteristics and send them to you because we believe they are consistent with what we have learned about your interests. To serve or target ads properly, a file called a web beacon may be included in these ads so that the networks may provide auditing, research, and reporting for advertisers and so that ads can be targeted to you while you are using other websites.

You may opt-out of use of web beacons in the OfficeArrow Website pages that you view by changing the settings in your web browser. If you opt-out of the use of such web beacons, the ads you receive from ad networks will not be tailored to your interests.

(d) Click-Through URLs

In some of the email messages we send you, we will include a "click-through URL" linked to relevant content on the OfficeArrow Website for your convenience. When you click on these links, you will pass through our servers as you are directed to the requested content. We track this "click-through" data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of these email messages. If you prefer not to have the information you view tracked in this way, you can opt-out of receiving these email communications by changing your options in the "My Dashboard" section of the OfficeArrow Website or you can choose not to click on the links in these emails.

### 1.3 Use of Collected Information

As described above, OfficeArrow collects personal information when you register with us, when you create or update your Profile, when you use the OfficeArrow Services, and when you visit and interact with the OfficeArrow Website.

(a) In General

In addition to the uses listed above, OfficeArrow uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to make recommendations for products and services that may interest you, to fulfill your requests for OfficeArrow Services and Service Provider Services, to improve the OfficeArrow Services, to contact you consistent with this Privacy Policy, to conduct research, to assist with systems administration, to resolve problems, to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients, and to facilitate your interaction with our Service Providers. We may also occasionally use your name and email address to notify you of OfficeArrow Services and Service Provider Services that we think you may find valuable and to notify you of administrative issues relevant to the OfficeArrow Website, such as the OfficeArrow Website being unavailable due to maintenance. You are free to opt-out of these administrative notifications or service notifications by changing your options in the "My Dashboard" section of the OfficeArrow Website; however, we will continue to contact you about your account or any orders you place.

On occasion, we will also combine information that we collect about you with information we obtain from Service Providers or other companies in order to provide you with offers, services, or information that we believe will be of interest to you.

### 2.0 Disclosure Of Your Information By OfficeArrow

In general, OfficeArrow may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a user has violated the [OfficeArrow Terms of Use](http://www.officearrow.com/terms_of_use), or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulation.

OfficeArrow is not in the business of selling your personal information to third parties, but there are times when it is advantageous for OfficeArrow to make certain information about you available to Service Providers to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process orders, deliver products, manage and enhance user data, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research. OfficeArrow may also share your information with third parties that you specifically select to receive your information when using an OfficeArrow Service. The manner in which we share your information with these third parties is discussed below.

### 2.1 Aggregate Information

In some instances, we will aggregate non-identifying user information and use this information ourselves or provide this information to other companies, including, for example, companies who market their products and services on the OfficeArrow Website. The recipients of this aggregated information may use it for varying purposes such as identifying and analyzing the shopping patterns or general interests of visitors to the OfficeArrow Website.

### 2.2 Third Party Advertisers

In addition to our Service Providers, OfficeArrow sometimes allows Service Providers to place third party advertisements on the OfficeArrow Website. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer or use other technologies such as web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. These mechanisms allow an advertising network to recognize your computer each time the advertising network sends you an advertisement in order to determine the effectiveness of its ads and to personalize advertising content. OfficeArrow does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

### 2.3 Other Third Party Service Providers

We may at times employ Service Providers to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer services. These Service Providers will have access to your personal information as needed to perform their functions, but we will contract with these Service Providers not to use your personal information for other purposes.

### 2.4 Your Consent

Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, you will receive notice when information about you, other than the information in your Public Profile, may be sent to third parties.

### 2.5 Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on OfficeArrow.

### 2.6 Business Transfers

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets or ownership interest of OfficeArrow, in part or in whole. Any third party to which we transfer or sell OfficeArrow's assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us in the same manner that OfficeArrow is allowed to use the information.

### 3.0 Links And Third Party Applications

### 3.1 Links

Throughout the OfficeArrow Website, we offer links to other websites that are not operated or controlled by OfficeArrow. OfficeArrow does not review and is not responsible for the policies and practices of other websites accessed by the links on the OfficeArrow Website, and any information you submit to those websites is subject to the privacy policies of the respective websites. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review its privacy and other policies.

### 3.2 Applications

Third party software applications created by third party developers are also available on the OfficeArrow Website. Third party applications are small bits of software, often with interactivity, that can be installed into your customized version of the OfficeArrow Website or even downloaded onto your computer. OfficeArrow does not control the third party developers who create these applications. When you engage with or download a third party application, you are interacting with such third party developer, not with us. OfficeArrow does not review and is not responsible for the policies and practices of third party developers, and we encourage you to ascertain and make sure you can trust such third parties before interacting with them by visiting their websites and reading their privacy and other policies.

### 4.0 Communications From The OfficeArrow Website

### 4.1 Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. You CANNOT opt-out of these communications unless you disable your OfficeArrow account.

### 4.2 Other Communications

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions using your provided name and email address. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletters to you. We will send you the OfficeArrow Website service related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You may be given the option to opt for or opt out of these communications.

### 5.0 Discussion Forums And User-Generated Content

One of the features of the OfficeArrow Website is a public discussion forum provided through discussion lists, bulletin boards or chat rooms (referred to as "Discussion Forums") to allow Participants with similar interests, fields of expertise or problems to share information and/or post and answer questions.

Any information that Participants disclose in the Discussion Forums is, by design, shared with the public and is not confidentially maintained. You should think carefully before disclosing any information, and particularly any personally identifiable information in the Discussion Forums. Because of the nature of the Discussion Forums, any information you disclose may be accessed, disclosed, or collected by third parties and as a result may be used by such third parties in ways that neither OfficeArrow nor you will be able to control or predict. You should not disclose any personally identifiable information about another person in the Discussion Forums.

OFFICEARROW IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OR ANY OTHER POSTINGS YOU OR OTHER USERS CHOOSE TO SUBMIT IN DISCUSSION FORUMS.

OfficeArrow reserves the right, but assumes no obligation, to monitor submissions and postings to the Discussion Forums; to record any such submissions; to disclose any information posted to the Discussion Forums or other portions of the OfficeArrow Website as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request; or to edit, refuse to post, or to remove any submitted information or materials, in OfficeArrow's sole discretion.

Your participation in the Discussion Forums, as well as your posting any other information, images, blog comments and other content on the OfficeArrow Website, is at your own risk and is governed by the OfficeArrow [OfficeArrow Terms of Use](http://www.officearrow.com/). Always remember, when you post private information in a public forum, it is no longer private information and cannot be removed entirely from the Internet.

### 6.0 Access To Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update, or delete your information by changing the information in the "My Dashboard" section of the OfficeArrow Website. If you want to terminate your account with OfficeArrow, you can deactivate your account from the "My Dashboard" section of the OfficeArrow Website. Additionally, you can email requests to correct, update or delete your information or deactivate your account to our Customer Support ([memberadvocate@officearrow.com](mailto:memberadvocate@officearrow.com)) or by contacting us at the following address or telephone number:

OfficeArrow, LLC  
2625 Cumberland Parkway, Suite 100  
Atlanta, GA 30339  
Attn: Member Advocate   
+1 (877) 277-6981

### 7.0 Security And Confidentiality

The security of your personal information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable efforts to keep your personally identifiable information, including, without limitation, financial information or credit card information, secure both during transmission and once we receive it. We endeavor to use appropriate physical, administrative, and technical security to protect against any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or inadequate disposal or destruction of personally identifiable information. When you transmit sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) to the OfficeArrow Website, we will signal your browser to encrypt that information using Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL). To make purchases through the OfficeArrow Website, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Safari to take advantage of this protection. OfficeArrow is not responsible for the security measures utilized by third party websites accessed by links from the OfficeArrow Website nor for the security measures utilized by Service Providers whose offers may be advertised on the OfficeArrow Website.

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your Profile, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and we cannot control the actions of other users or third parties with whom you may choose to share your pages and information, including by making your Profile Public. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that the information you include in your Profile or otherwise post on the OfficeArrow Website will be completely confidential or will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the OfficeArrow Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of user content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or on the systems of other users if such users have copied or stored your user content.

If you have any questions about security on the OfficeArrow Website, you can send us an email at[privacy@officearrow.com](mailto:privacy@officearrow.com).

### 8.0 Children

OfficeArrow does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information about anyone under the age of 18, nor do we knowingly provide recommendations to such persons. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for OfficeArrow or send any information about yourself to us.

No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the OfficeArrow Website. In the event that we learn that we have mistakenly collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have information from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at [privacy@officearrow.com](mailto:privacy@officearrow.com).

### 9.0 International Use

Information that is submitted to the OfficeArrow Website will be collected, processed, stored, disclosed and disposed of in accordance with the applicable United States laws and this Privacy Policy. If you are a non-United States user, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your information and disclose it to other entities outside your resident jurisdiction, as discussed in this Privacy Policy. In addition, such information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. United States law may not provide the degree of protection for personal information that is available in other countries. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy, understand it, and agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and have already provided us with information, please email us at the contact listed below and ask us to delete your information and deactivate your account.

### 10.0 Terms Of Use, Notices And Changes To This Privacy Policy

Your visit to, registration with, and use of the OfficeArrow Website, and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes or clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the OfficeArrow Website. If we make changes, we will post them to the OfficeArrow Website and will indicate at the bottom of this Privacy Policy the effective date. Your use of the OfficeArrow Website after the effective date indicates your acceptance of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

### 11.0 Questions or Comments

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@officearrow.com](mailto:privacy@officearrow.com). You may also contact us by mail at:

OfficeArrow, LLC  
Attn: Customer Service  
2625 Cumberland Parkway  
Suite 100  
Atlanta, GA 30339
